http://www.allgospellyrics.com/privacypolicy.html

AllGospelLyrics.com - Privacy Statement
Personal Information:
AllGospelLyrics.com is committed to protecting your privacy online. We are also committed to providing you with the very best experience we can on our web site. In order to enhance your experience at our sites we gather certain personal information about you that helps us customize our content to your tastes and preferences. We may ask for your name, e-mail address, and country.
By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by AllGospelLyrics.com as outlined in this privacy policy. AllGospelLyrics.com does not sell, rent, or trade your personal information with any third party unless specified.
IP address and logging:
Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information and to track your general visiting patterns (how many pages you view while at one website, downloads, etc).
Advertising;
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit AllGospelLyrics.com. These companies may use information (no personal information) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.
Cookies:
From time to time, AllGospelLyrics.com or its advertisers may send a cookie to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web
server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Cookies do not damage your system.
We use cookies to identify which areas of AllGospelLyrics.com you have visited. Our advertisers may also use cookies to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. Our advertisers and we may use this information to better personalize the content of our site.
You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you
when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.
Disclaimer:
This is an information tool provided by at no charge to the user. AllGospelLyrics.com makes no warranties, expressed or implied, for the services we provide. AllGospelLyrics.com will not be held responsible for any damages you or your business may suffer from using AllGospelLyrics.com services. AllGospelLyrics.com will not be held responsible for any interruptions, delays, failures, inaccuracies, or typographical errors. AllGospelLyrics.com does not represent or warrant that the Service or the server that makes it available, are free of viruses or other harmful components. AllGospelLyrics.com does not warrant or represent that the use or the results of the use of the Service or the materials made available as part of the Service will be correct, accurate, timely, or otherwise reliable. AllGospelLyrics.com realizes that there are thousands of illegally distributed copyrighted material on the Internet. All the lyrics listed on this site are property of their respective owners and are strictly for educational or personal use only. Commercial use is prohibited without the owners' consent. AllGospelLyrics.com
is a not-for-profit resource. All advertising proceeds are used to maintain its
servers and other costs associated with website maintenance and upkeep. AllGospelLyrics.com
does not endorse the distribution of copyrighted content. When you download or use lyrics from AllGospelLyrics.com web site you do so with the understanding that AllGospelLyrics.com and its operators will not be held accountable or responsible for violations of copyright or intellectual property laws that may occur as a result of your action.
Liability:
It is AllGospelLyrics.com's policy to respond quickly to claims of intellectual property violation. Upon receiving notification in accordance with any related copyright organization or owner, AllGospelLyrics.com will immediately disable and remove lyrics in question. To report illegal content please mail us at mskeke@{remove*this*text}gmail.com
